vrdialog.com 2018-11-21

# APPLICATION PRIVACY POLICY – VR DIALOG

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to the treatment of personally identifiable information submitted by, or otherwise obtained from, you in connection with the associated application (“Application”). The Application is provided by VRDialog (and may be signed by Hexagon3D or Electronic-Marketing brand owned by VRDialog). By using or otherwise accessing the Application, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement.

#### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES VRDialog COLLECT?

We **do not collect** your personal information. We may see any information you submit to Facebook fanpage related with the Application. The types of personal information may include just informations already published by you on your Facebook page.

#### CAN CHILDREN USE THE APPLICATION?

Our site and the services available through VRDialog are not intended for children under the age of 13.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

VRDialog may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Statement when he or she uses or otherwise accesses the Application after such changes have been first posted.

#### QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at info(at)e-marketing.pl. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.  
Effective Date: April 1, 2014
